jazeeraairways.com 2006-06-16

# Jazeera Airways - Privacy

  * What is Jazeera Airway's Privacy Policy?
  * What personal data do we collect?
  * What do we use your personal data for?
  * Disclosure to third parties
  * How can you amend your personal details?
  * How does Jazeera Airways protect your personal data?
  * Use of Cookies

**What is Jazeera Airway's Privacy Policy?**

**Jazeera Airways** strongly believes in the protection and privacy of your personal data. **Jazeera Airways** takes great care to at all times act in compliance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains how Jazeera Airways collates, uses and protects personal information that we process about you. From time to time it may be necessary to update this policy. We will notify you of any such updates by posting such updates on the **Jazeera Airways** website. The Privacy Policy does not cover any third party website that you may enter via the **Jazeera Airways** website. 

**What personal data do we collect?**

When you make a booking with **Jazeera Airways** , we require you to provide us with certain personal data to allow us to provide our services to you. The information we collect may include your payment card details, contact details (including name, address, email addresses and telephone numbers) and details of other passengers on the booking (when providing information about other passengers, please ensure that they have consented to this). We may also collect your contact details and preferences during any competitions or promotional activities that we carry out. **Jazeera Airways** does not collect any sensitive personal information. The information collected is stored on our secure servers which are located in the USA and Canada. 

**What do we use your personal data for?**

**Jazeera Airways** uses your personal data for the purpose of allowing us to provide our services to you and to process your booking requests. We use your personal data so as to allow us to contact you in case of queries or amendments to flight details. Where you have given us your consent to use your personal data, we may provide you with further information as to our products and services. 

**Disclosure to third parties**

**Jazeera Airways** will not provide your personal data to any unrelated third parties, save for where we are required to do so by law; in order to administer your booking (including debiting your payment card); where it is necessary to safeguard the proper operation of our systems; where required to protect ourselves and our customers; where required for business succession reasons or where you have permitted us to do so. 

**Jazeera Airways** may provide collated customer and traffic statistics to third parties but these statistics will not contain any information that can personally identify a customer.

**Jazeera Airways** may need to pass your data to selected third parties in order to facilitate associated transactions such as car and hotel bookings. 

**How does Jazeera Airways protect your personal data?**

**Jazeera Airways** uses up to date industry procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorised access, use, disclosure or loss. When booking a flight with **Jazeera Airways** the personal information provided to us is held securely on servers in the USA and Canada using security measures that are consistent with best Internet practice. 

To ensure the security of your payment card information we use the latest Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. If your browser supports SSL, please select the Secure Mode option when confirming your booking. If you are restricted by the capabilities of your browser then you can use the non-secure mode but we recommend that you upgrade to the latest version of any browser to give you extra reassurance during any further transactions.

**Use of Cookies**

From time to time, **Jazeera Airways** may use 'Cookies'. Cookies are small pieces of information which can be stored on your computer's hard drive. They allow you to access additional features on the **Jazeera Airways** website and to provide you with a more personalised booking experience. You can, if you wish, delete these Cookies from your hard drive.
